## Alireza Kavian

#### C.E.O at Brilacasck

Website: https://alireza-kavian.github.io
Email: alireza.kavian7@gmail.com

Also known as @alireza\_kay or @alirezakay on social networks.

So far, I've passed 3 years of university.

In free times, I do learn more about my favourite fields like web development, User Interface/Experience and researching the relevant issues.

I gained experience through various projects of University in several fields of #CE My major skill is on **front-end** development.

To know more about my works, take a look at my linkedin and brilacasck corp.

I'd like to expand my experiences, every day :)

Also to study at the 'University Of Toronto' in Canada OR' ETH Zurich' in switzerland some day

Experience

#### C.E.O at Brilacasck

JULY 2017 - PRESENT

Chief Execution Officer

#### **Brilacasck**

In 2017 I founded this company alongside with my friend @soheilch.

To gain more experience, we've done diverse projects in different fields of our courses together in university.

Then after a year with another friend ours (@amirhkh), we did extend our team.

After that we are a young small team with full of creativity and incentives.

A self-employed organization working in the way of **Agile development.** 

### Developer Internship at Ysorkh

JULY 2018 - PRESENT

Developer

#### **Ysorkh**

I've got my internship in some fields of **Network/Web Security**, **Web SEO** and **Professional Web Development** for deciding what would be the best to concentrate on.

#### Education

### K. N. Toosi University of Technology

2015 - PRESENT

Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering,

In 2015, I got entered to the university with great inducements for progressing Till now my total average grade has been: **18.43** ( of 20 )

KNTU University In Tehran, Iran

#### Skills

#### **Global Skills**

- Scrum Project Management
- Team Management
- Idea Performer
- Teaching
- Soccer (GoalKeeping | Defending)
- Ping-Pong

#### **Programming**

- Industry Knowledge
  - Front-End Development
  - Web Development
  - Software Engineering
  - AVR Programming
  - PhotoShop
  - o 3D Max
  - Microsoft Office (powerpoint word excel)
  - o Agile Developing

#### Tools And Technologies

- Javascript
- o CSS
- Linux
- HTML
- IQuery
- ReactJS
- AngularJS
- Bootstrap
- o PHP
- SQL
- Python
- 。 C
- o C++
- Intel X86 Assembly (NASM)
- AVR Assembly
- Android
- VHDL

Certifications

### Web Designing (Front-End)

NOVEMBER 2017

University Of Tehran

Most concentrate on **html** / **css** / **javascript** / **jquery** 

*Volunteerings* 

### K. N. Toosi University of Technology

OCTOBOR 2017 TO JANUARY

Science And Technology

Role: **Undergraduate Teaching Assistant**Course: Theory of Language and Automaton

Professor: Dr. S.H. Khaasteh

## K. N. Toosi University of Technology

FEBRUARY 2018 TO JUNE 2018

Science And Technology

Role: Undergraduate Teaching Assistant

Course: Compiler

Professor: Dr. S. Sedighian Kashi.

## K. N. Toosi University of Technology

FEBRUARY 2018 TO JUNE 2018

Science And Technology

Role: Undergraduate Teaching Assistant

Course: Assembly Language (x86 Intel assembly language)

Professor: Dr. B. Nasihatkon

**Projects** 

# Simulating A Simple Text Editor With C Language

TERM 1 - 2015

https://alirezakay.github.io/showcase/term1

With using c / c++ language and also BGI graphical library for my first main programming major project

# Simulating Graphical Plant Grwoth With Java

TERM 2 - 2016

https://alirezakay.github.io/showcase/term2

Using OOP (object oriented programming) in java Language and also graphical java framework JavaFX

### Implementing DFS/BFS Algorithms With

TERM 2 - 2016

### Java

https://alirezakay.github.io/showcase/term2

Using java / javaFX to commit this algorithms to an non-directed graph

# Implementing A Simple Java Parser With Java Language

TERM 3 - 2016

https://alirezakay.github.io/showcase/term3

A simple compiler for java language for detecting typical errors using CFG (context free grammars) and CYK algorithm.

Implemented with java language

# Implementing A Graphical Chess Game WithJava

TERM 4 - 2017

https://alirezakay.github.io/showcase/term4

A nearly pleasant graphical chess game implemented with java language and using JavaFX & JavaAWT.

Algorithms: min-max-tree & alpha-beta-game-tree

# Simulating A Plenary CPU Using MIPS Concepts With VHDL

TERM 4 - 2017

https://alirezakay.github.io/showcase/term4

A MIPS-like processor implemented in VHDL language. (RISC CPU)

### Creating A Full Compiler With Java

TERM 5 - 2017

https://alirezakay.github.io/showcase/term5

Using compiler concepts to create a complete compiler for parsing any languages you want to invent.

Using java / JavaFX

# Creating An Online Shopping Website Using MySQL And PHP

TERM 5 - 2017

https://alirezakay.github.io/showcase/term5

A website like: digikala

implemented for the course 'Database' With PHP, MySQL, Apache, Bootstrap

## Simulating Micro Processor Communication With SystemC Language

TERM 6-2018

https://alirezakay.github.io/showcase/term6

Communication between micro-processor and accelerator with shared memory in a bus context.

Using SystemC language for hardware-software co-design simulation

#### Created using Resumonk - Online Resume Builder

## Tiny Courseware System For Computer Engineers (TCS4CE)

MARCH 2018 TO JUNE 2018

https://alirezakay.github.io/showcase/term6

This project was going to be implemented for the course **Software Engineering** on aweb context.

I started implementation alongside my two other **team mates**. a trio team.

It was a good chance to expose the result of this project to the authorities of our college.

This project is a system for creating courses by teachers / compiling and running codes by students and get score at the same moment.

a handy courseware.

Languages

**Persian** (Native), **English** (Professional working proficiency), **Arabic** (Limited working proficiency)